[
 {
   "question": "Where is the giant pendulum on campus?",
   "answer": "Mitchell Physics Building",
   "answer_choices": [
      "Mitchell Physics Building",
      "Mitchell Physics Undergraduate Building",
      "Chemistry Building",
      "Zachry Engineering Building"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "This pendulum swings freely and is moved by the rotation of the Earth."
},
 {
   "question": "Where can you find George R.R Martin manuscripts of Game of Thrones?",
   "answer": "Cushing Memorial Library",
   "answer_choices": [
      "Cushing Memorial Library",
      "Evans Library",
      "Medical Sciences Library",
      "West Campus Library"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "This library hosts historical artifacts and rotating exhibits. Check out their website to figure out what they have on display now."
},
 {
   "question": "What is the oldest tree on campus?",
   "answer": "Century Tree",
   "answer_choices": [
      "Century Tree",
      "Decade Tree",
      "Millenial Tree",
      "Tree of the Ages"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "Considered one of the most romantic places on campus, Aggie couples have been getting engaged under this tree for decades. "
},
 {
   "question": "Which U.S. President is buried near campus?",
   "answer": "George H. W. Bush",
   "answer_choices": [
      "George H. W. Bush",
      "Lyndon Baynes Johnson",
      "George W. Bush",
      "Dwight D. Eisenhower"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "He and his wife were buried within 4 months of each other."
},
 {
   "question": "Texas A&M has a football team member that stays ready to help his teammates, what is he called?",
   "answer": "12th Man",
   "answer_choices": [
      "12th Man",
      "The Other Man",
      "Lieutenant Dan",
      "2nd Man"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "Now, the student body carries on his spirit by standing for the entirety of our football games."
},
 {
   "question": "What is the name of Texas A&Mâ€™s mascot?",
   "answer": "Reveille",
   "answer_choices": [
      "Reveille",
      "Bevo",
      "The Masked Raider",
      "Uga"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "The tradition of having a dog for our mascot started in 1931 when a dog was adopted by the Corps of Cadets."
},
 {
   "question": "What is the commonly placed item at the base of Sully's statue before an exam?",
   "answer": "A penny",
   "answer_choices": [
      "A penny",
      "A quarter",
      "A notecard",
      "A piece of gum"
   ],
   "fun_facts": "When Sullivent Ross was president, he would leave his office door open, welcoming students with \"a penny for your thoughts.\""
},
 {
   "question": "In honor of the fallen aggies who have passed, our monthly tradition is to come together during which event?",
   "answer": "SilverTaps",
   "answer_choices": [
      "SilverTaps",
      "Fallen Aggies",
      "Golden Taps",
      "Aggie Muster"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "Who should you call, if you have a question about you transcript",
   "answer": "979 845 1066",
   "answer_choices": [
      "979 845 1066",
      "911",
      "979 845 3236",
      "979 458 8310"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "What year student is the handler of Reveille?",
   "answer": "Sophomore",
   "answer_choices": [
      "Sophomore",
      "Freshman",
      "Junior",
      "Senior"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "What year was the first female handler elected?",
   "answer": "2018",
   "answer_choices": [
      "2018",
      "2017",
      "2019",
      "2020"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "Where can you go on campus, if you issues with your technology, or need to buy new technology?",
   "answer": "12th Man Technology",
   "answer_choices": [
      "12th Man Technology",
      "Zachary",
      "ETB Building",
      "Best Buy"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "What is the number for getting a Corp Escort?",
   "answer": "979 845 6789",
   "answer_choices": [
      "979 845 6789",
      "979 458 8250",
      "979 845 2345",
      "979 845 8300"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "Which Reveille was the first full-blooded Rough Collie?",
   "answer": "III",
   "answer_choices": [
      "III",
      "II",
      "I",
      "IV"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
},
 {
   "question": "Where can you get your textbooks?",
   "answer": "Barnes and Noble - MSC",
   "answer_choices": [
      "Barnes and Noble - MSC",
      "Cushing Library",
      "Zachary",
      "Bright Building"
   ],
   "fun_facts": ""
}
]